Guide to Great Powers Seminar: The United States Audio-Visual Recordings
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Great powers seminar: the United States audio-visual recordings
1982
SC1134
Stanford Alumni Association
0.5 Linear feet
Videotapes and audiorecordings of events during the seminar, including a talk by William Chace on "Images of Contemporary America in Literature," and a panel on "The State of the Arts and Humanities in the United States" with Richard W. Lyman, president of the Rockefeller Foundation, and three Stanford professors, Morris Zelditch, Wanda Corn, and William Chace.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Administrative transfer, 1995.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Description of the Collection
Videotapes and audiorecordings of events during the seminar, including a talk by William Chace on "Images of Contemporary America in Literature," and a panel on "The State of the Arts and Humanities in the United States" with Richard W. Lyman, president of the Rockefeller Foundation, and three Stanford professors, Morris Zelditch, Wanda Corn, and William Chace.
Access Terms
Chace, William M.; Corn, Wanda M.; Lyman, Richard W., 1923-2012.; Stanford Alumni Association; Zelditch, Morris.; American literature.; Humanities--United States.; Videorecordings.
Collection Contents
- Videorecordings, 2 videotape(s) (u-matic)
  - Panel: "The State of the Arts and Humanities in the United States" (William Chace, Wanda Corn, Richard W. Lyman, Morris Zelditch, Jr.), 1982 Apr 18; 1.1; 1 videotape(s) (U-matic) (Box 1)
    Corn, Wanda M.; Lyman, Richard W., 1923-2012.; Zelditch, Morris.
  - William Chace, "Images of Contemporary America in Literature", 1982 Apr 18; 1.2; 1 videotape(s) (U-matic) (Box 1)
- Audiorecordings
  - #1 Kennedy & Boskin; #2 Boskin, 1982; 1.3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - #3 Boskin; #4 Panel, 1982; 1.4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - #5 Panel; #6 Danelski, 1982; 1.5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - #7 Danelski; #8 Panel (Kaplan, Degler, Atkin), 1982; 1.6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - #13-14 Panel: "The State of the Arts and Humanities in the United States" (William Chace, Wanda Corn, Richard W. Lyman, Morris Zelditch, 1982; 1.7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - #19-20 Panel: George, Wirth, Lewis, Abernethy, Goldstein, 1982; 1.8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)